[{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678855024,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":8938,"timeElapsed":43741},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678860330,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":5272,"timeElapsed":49048},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678867441,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":7071,"timeElapsed":56152},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678875188,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":7710,"timeElapsed":63904},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678878005,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2779,"timeElapsed":66720},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678881410,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":3369,"timeElapsed":70125},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678883974,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":2528,"timeElapsed":72692},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678891356,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":7342,"timeElapsed":80070},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678896000,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4610,"timeElapsed":84718},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678915542,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":18234,"timeElapsed":104260},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678918208,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2629,"timeElapsed":106924},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678922051,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3805,"timeElapsed":110766},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678925893,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":3802,"timeElapsed":114610},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678930236,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":4308,"timeElapsed":118953},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678932419,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2147,"timeElapsed":121136},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678934158,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":1705,"timeElapsed":122875},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678940816,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":6623,"timeElapsed":129533},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678944234,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":3384,"timeElapsed":132952},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678953766,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":8379,"timeElapsed":142484},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678956143,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2346,"timeElapsed":144863},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678957905,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":1731,"timeElapsed":146623},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678959257,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":1320,"timeElapsed":147976},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678960928,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":1639,"timeElapsed":149645},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678962656,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":1693,"timeElapsed":151373},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678964556,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1866,"timeElapsed":153275},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678966724,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":2131,"timeElapsed":155437},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678968764,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":2006,"timeElapsed":157481},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678978781,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":8905,"timeElapsed":167498},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678980551,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":1731,"timeElapsed":169264},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678982715,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2121,"timeElapsed":171431},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678984611,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1865,"timeElapsed":173330},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678986654,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2012,"timeElapsed":175373},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678988442,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1755,"timeElapsed":177158},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678990448,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1975,"timeElapsed":179168},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678993697,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3213,"timeElapsed":182410},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678996245,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2509,"timeElapsed":184961},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679005690,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":8403,"timeElapsed":194408},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679007372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":1652,"timeElapsed":196091},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679009627,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2220,"timeElapsed":198344},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679011323,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1665,"timeElapsed":200043},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679013259,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1902,"timeElapsed":201979},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679015041,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":1748,"timeElapsed":203759},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679016811,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":1735,"timeElapsed":205529},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679019828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":2979,"timeElapsed":208545},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679021888,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":2026,"timeElapsed":210607},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679028166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":5356,"timeElapsed":216884},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679030427,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2227,"timeElapsed":219143},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679032780,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":2324,"timeElapsed":221500},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679034685,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":1872,"timeElapsed":223402},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679037149,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2432,"timeElapsed":225868},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679039305,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2121,"timeElapsed":228022},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679041987,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2647,"timeElapsed":230702},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679043894,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":1876,"timeElapsed":232613},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679045994,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2066,"timeElapsed":234710},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679050057,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3238,"timeElapsed":238775},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679051637,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1547,"timeElapsed":240353},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679053611,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1933,"timeElapsed":242328},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679055329,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1684,"timeElapsed":244046},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679056971,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1610,"timeElapsed":245689},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679058800,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1793,"timeElapsed":247518},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679060895,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2063,"timeElapsed":249612},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679064359,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":3430,"timeElapsed":253076},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679067076,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":2681,"timeElapsed":255792},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679074891,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":6954,"timeElapsed":263608},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679076547,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":1621,"timeElapsed":265263},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679078058,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":1478,"timeElapsed":266777},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679083944,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5851,"timeElapsed":272659},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679087892,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":3918,"timeElapsed":276612},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679093544,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":5615,"timeElapsed":282256},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679096624,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3046,"timeElapsed":285342},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679098603,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1945,"timeElapsed":287320},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679103034,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4395,"timeElapsed":291750},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679105584,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2516,"timeElapsed":294301},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679114887,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":8426,"timeElapsed":303605},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679116851,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1924,"timeElapsed":305563},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679120423,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":3534,"timeElapsed":309141},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679122635,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2178,"timeElapsed":311352},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679125699,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":3030,"timeElapsed":314416},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679127762,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":2030,"timeElapsed":316480},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679129765,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1968,"timeElapsed":318483},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679133855,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":4058,"timeElapsed":322574},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679135754,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1866,"timeElapsed":324471},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679139254,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3466,"timeElapsed":327971},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679146582,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":6120,"timeElapsed":335300},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679148430,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":1815,"timeElapsed":337148},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679150487,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2022,"timeElapsed":339204},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679151972,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":1450,"timeElapsed":340690},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679155521,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3514,"timeElapsed":344238},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679157507,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1953,"timeElapsed":346224},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679159384,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":1842,"timeElapsed":348100},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679163820,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4401,"timeElapsed":352537},{"subjectID":"jsoe85jztm","prolificID":"6763836f14cdd13de817ecda","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4873cbbee544bd3843","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679165350,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1494,"timeElapsed":354067}]